Privacy Policy
==============

Clorox and [its family of brands](https://www.thecloroxcompany.com/brands/) (collectively, “we,” “us,” “our”) have a strong tradition of honesty and fair dealing and we strive to be transparent about our privacy practices. We provide this Privacy Policy to help you understand how we collect, use, share, and safeguard your personal information. This Privacy Policy also tells you about your rights and choices with respect to your personal information, and how you can reach us to get answers to questions you may have about our privacy practices.

This information may be updated from time to time.

What’s Contained in This Privacy Policy
---------------------------------------

You can jump to particular topics by going to the headings below:

* * *

Types of Information We Collect
-------------------------------

We collect information about you in a variety of ways depending on how you interact with us and our products and services, including through our websites, social media pages, online and mobiles services, applications and advertisements. Some of the information we collect includes personal information that can be used to identify you. The following provides an overview of the types of information we collect from various sources. For details about the information (including non-exhaustive examples) we collect and how we use that information, you can read more on the [**Types of Information We Collect page**](https://www.thecloroxcompany.com/privacy/information-we-collect/).

* **Information You Provide to Us.** We collect information that you provide to us directly, such as when you register for an account, subscribe to receive our communications, enter contests or sweepstakes, make purchases, contact us with questions or comments, apply for a job, or participate in our online forums, promotions and social media platforms.
* **Device Information.** We use technologies to collect information from your devices (computers, mobile phones, tablets, etc.) when you visit our websites or download and use our mobile applications. This information could include your IP address, device advertising ID, information about your device’s/browser’s operating system, how you use the application or device, and your physical location.
* **Location Information.** Some of our websites may collect information about your general location, such as your ZIP code or address, in order to locate stores that sell our products or provide other location-related services.
* **Information from Cookies and Other Similar Tracking Technologies.** We use cookies and other similar technologies, such as web beacons, clear GIFs, pixels and internet tag technologies (collectively, “tracking technologies”), to gather certain information related to the ways you interact with our websites, mobile applications, advertising, and/or email communications. This information may include browser type, browsing behaviors, user web requests, pages and content viewed, the number of new visits or log-ins, search engine referral, affiliate referrals, traffic driven by banner ads or other promotions, which items are placed in shopping carts and which are abandoned, conversions and what purchases were made, and ZIP codes. Additionally, we may monitor and analyze your activity on our websites and mobile applications to improve your experience, which may include the use of third-party session replay software or services. For details about the types of tracking technologies we use, you can read more on the [Cookies and Other Similar Tracking Technologies page](https://www.thecloroxcompany.com/privacy/information-we-collect/#cookies).
* **Information from Other Sources.** In addition to the information that we collect from you directly, we may also receive information about you from other sources, including third parties, such as our business partners, our affiliates, publicly available sources, or social networks in which you participate. For example, we collect certain information that is posted on social media sites, blogs and other websites.

* * *

How We Use and Process Information
----------------------------------

We use the information we collect to deliver, personalize, and improve our products and services, as well as to understand how you use and interact with our websites and applications. In addition to the purposes and uses described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we generally use information in the following ways:

* **To provide you access to our websites and applications**, including to service your accounts and maintain the security of your accounts.
* **To provide you with products and services**, including to complete transactions you have requested or fulfill orders you have placed.
* **To respond to or communicate with you**, including to follow-up on your comments, reviews, inquiries and other requests; to communicate with you about contests, sweepstakes, loyalty or rewards programs, coupons, rebates, promotions or other matters which you have entered or joined or for which you have requested information; and to communicate with you about your account.
* **For marketing and advertising**, including to send advertising or marketing communications about products, services, offers, promotions, rewards, and events, and provide news and information that we believe may be of interest to you.
* **For analytics**, including to conduct research and analysis related to our businesses, websites, products and services, including combining information we collect to identify other potential customers (e.g., “look alike” customers).
* **To personalize your experience with us**, including to tailor our products and services to your usage or preferences.
* **To maintain interactive features**, including to implement social networking features you have activated; and to publish your reviews, comments, photos, videos and other content you have posted to one of our interactive or user-generated features.
* **For business purposes**, including to operate and improve our business and business activities; to manage our relationships; to detect and prevent fraud or misuse of our services; and for any other business purpose permitted by law.
* **For such other purposes as you may consent** (from time to time).
* **For legal and safety purposes**, including to defend or protect us, you, our customers, or third parties, from harm or in legal proceedings; maintain the security of our customers, employees, and property; respond to court orders, lawsuits, subpoenas, and government requests; address legal and regulatory compliance; and as otherwise permitted or required by applicable law.

To the extent we maintain and use personal information in a deidentified form, we will not attempt to reidentify the information, except for the purpose of determining whether our deidentification processes satisfy our legal obligations.

* * *

How We Share Information
------------------------

In addition to the specific situations discussed elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we disclose information in the following situations as permitted by law:

* **Affiliates.** Where permitted by law, and as consistent with the purposes identified in this Privacy Policy, we may share information with our family of brands and corporate affiliates (e.g., parent company, sister companies, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control).
* **Corporate Transaction.** We may disclose your information to a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, acquisition, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, including at the negotiation stage.
* **Business Partners.** We may share your information with business partners, such as a third-party intermediary to comply with your request for the shipment of products or the provision of services.
* **Advertising Vendors.** We may share your information with third parties that support our advertising and marketing efforts, including for purposes of behavioral advertising.
* **Service Providers.** We may share your information with service providers who perform services on our behalf. Among other things, service providers may help us to administer our website, assist or support our business operations (including customer service providers, loyalty program administrators, product review hosts, and  surveys administrators), provide technical support and information technology and security programs, conduct research and analysis, process payments, assist in the management and fulfillment of orders, assist with fraud prevention, detection, and mitigation, and provide marketing and data analytics.
* **Legal Process.** We may disclose information in response to subpoenas, warrants, or court orders, or in connection with any legal process, to comply with relevant laws, or to respond to requests from public and government authorities. We may also share your information in order to enforce our terms and conditions, to establish or exercise our rights, to defend against a legal claim, to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding possible illegal activities, suspected fraud, safety of person or property, or a violation of our policies, or to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates.
* **Public.** We may offer community features and public interactive forums through our websites, such as discussion boards, product reviews, chat rooms, forums, wikis, social networking platforms and blogs. If you decide to submit information on these pages, that information may be publicly available.
* **Partner Promotion.** We may offer contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions with third-party partners. If you decide to enter a contest, sweepstakes, or promotion that is sponsored by a third-party partner the information that you provide will be shared with us and with them. Their use of your information is not governed by this Privacy Policy.
* **Wedding, Baby, and/or Gift Registry.** Some of our websites provide the opportunity to create public registries where you can indicate to others what types of products you might be interested in receiving. The information that you provide about your event (_e.g.,_ name, date, location, etc.) as part of a public registry may be publicly available to permit your guests to search for your registry. In some cases, we may provide you with options to restrict the extent to which that information will be made available to the public. We may also share your information with third-party wedding and gift registry portal sites. Among other things this provides your guests with additional means of finding your registry and coordinating gifts.
* **Other Disclosures with Your Consent.** We may ask if you would like us to share your information with other third parties who are not described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy.

Click [here](https://www.thecloroxcompany.com/privacy/how-we-share-information) for a description of the categories of information we disclose for a “business purpose” and share for purposes of cross-context behavioral advertising (also referred to as “targeted advertising”) (as those terms are defined by applicable law). Please note that because this list is comprehensive it may refer to types of information that we share about people other than yourself. Note that we do not “sell” your personal information for money. As discussed elsewhere in the Privacy Policy, we use cookies and similar tracking technologies, as well as share email addresses and other non-cookie personal information, for purposes of behavioral advertising. Under applicable law, this may be considered a “sale.” For more information, please refer to the [Cookies and Other Similar Tracking Technologies page](https://www.thecloroxcompany.com/privacy/information-we-collect/#cookies).

* * *

Your Choices
------------

Depending on your state and country of residence, you can make the following choices regarding your personal information:

* **Access to Your Personal Information.** You may request confirmation on whether we are processing your personal information and request access to the personal information that we have about you, including related information, or a copy of that information, by following the instructions described in the Contact Information section below. In certain circumstances, you may request portability of your personal information. If required by law, upon request, we will grant you reasonable access to the personal information that we have about you.
* **Changes to Your Personal Information.** You may request your personal information be corrected. Note that we rely on you to update and correct your personal information. Most of our websites allow you to modify or delete your account profile. Note that we may keep historical information in our backup files as permitted by law. If our website does not permit you to update or correct certain information, contact us by following the instructions described in the Contact Information section below.
* **Deletion of Your Personal Information.** You may request that we delete your personal information by following the instructions described in the Contact Information section below. If required by law we will grant a request to delete information, but you should note that in certain situations, we may be required or permitted by law to keep your personal information.
* **Objection to Certain Processing.** In some circumstances, you may object to our processing of your personal information by following the instructions described in the Contact Information section below.
* **Restriction of Processing.** In certain limited circumstances, you may request that we restrict processing your personal information by following the instructions described in the Contact Information section below.
* **Revocation of Consent.** If you revoke your consent for the processing of personal information then we may no longer be able to provide you services. You may revoke consent to processing (where such processing is based upon consent) by following the instructions described in the Contact Information section below.
* **Do Not Track (“DNT”) Feature.** We do not currently recognize the “Do Not Track” signal.
* **Direct Marketing Communications.** We will only use your personal information for our direct marketing purposes and/or share your personal information with third parties for our direct marketing purposes as specified in this Privacy Policy. For example, you may choose to provide us with your email address or mailing address for the purpose of allowing us to send free newsletters, surveys, offers, and other promotional materials to you, as well as targeted offers from third parties. You may request to opt-out/unsubscribe from direct marketing communications at any time by contacting us using the information in the Contact Information section below, or by clicking the unsubscribe link within the email we sent. If you receive a text message from us that contains promotional information you can opt-out of receiving future text messages by replying “STOP,” “UNSUBSCRIBE” or other similar responses as described in the text message. You can stop receiving physical mail offers by emailing us with “NO SNAIL MAIL” in the subject line along with your name, address and ZIP code. We will process your opt-out/unsubscribe request in accordance with applicable laws and without charge. If you decide not to receive promotional offers, we may still send you service-related communications. Please note that our mailings are prepared in advance of their being sent. Although we will remove your name from our mailing list after receiving your request, you may still receive mailings from us that had been initiated prior to your name being removed.
* **Cookies and Similar Tracking Technologies.** Most web browsers allow you to reject or delete cookies through their settings preferences. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our websites. For more information about how certain of our websites use cookies and, where applicable, to update your preferences, click the “Cookie Settings” link available on the applicable website.
* **Opt-Out of Targeted Advertising/Sharing**. You may opt-out of the processing of your personal information for targeted advertising/sharing of your personal information for purposes of cross-context behavioral advertising. To opt-out, please click the “Your Privacy Choices” link on the applicable homepage. We also recognize Global Privacy Control (GPC) signals and other user-enabled opt-out preference signals as valid opt-out requests where required by applicable law. Please note that your opt-out preference signal will be applied only to your current browser and device. To learn more about the GPC, you can visit its website [here](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/).

**Submitting Requests**

In some cases, we may limit or deny your request if the law permits or requires us to do so, or if we are unable to adequately verify your identity. We do not discriminate against individuals who exercise their privacy rights under applicable law. If we deny or fail to take action on your request, you may appeal our decision by contacting us at [privacyinfo@clorox.com](mailto:privacyinfo@clorox.com "mailto:privacyinfo@clorox.com") with the subject line “Appeal.”

Please note that to protect your information we must be able to verify your identity before we can process your request to exercise any of the foregoing privacy rights. We may conduct the verification process by email or phone, and we may ask you to provide information such as your name, contact information, and any additional relevant information based on your relationship with us.

In some circumstances, certain individuals may designate an authorized agent to submit requests to exercise certain privacy rights on their behalf. To do so, you must provide that authorized agent written and signed permission to submit the request on your behalf and verify your own identity directly with us. Note that we may deny a request from an authorized agent that does not submit proof that they have been authorized by you to act on your behalf.

If you are an authorized agent submitting a request on behalf of another person, you must attach a copy of a completed [Authorized Agent Designation](https://www.thecloroxcompany.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Clorox_Authorized-Agent-Designation-Form-Updated-for-CPRA.pdf) form indicating that you are able to act on that other person’s behalf.

* * *

How We Protect and Retain Information
-------------------------------------

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is fully secure. While we use reasonable efforts to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information. In the event that we are required by law to inform you of a breach affecting your personal information we may notify you electronically, in writing, or by telephone, if permitted to do so by law.

Additionally, we maintain internal governance policies designed to protect your personal information. These governance policies cover topics including, but not limited to, information security, incident response, data subject rights, and record retention and destruction.

Some of our websites permit you to create an account. When you do you will be prompted to create a password. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password, selecting a strong password and constructing a unique password. You are responsible for any access to or use of your account by someone else that has obtained your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by you. You should notify us of any unauthorized use of your password or account.

We retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. To determine the appropriate retention period for personal information, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the information, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of the information, the purposes for which we obtained the information and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, as well as applicable legal requirements.

* * *

Other Important Information
---------------------------

The following additional information relates to our privacy practices:

* **Children.** Our websites and online services are not intended for children under the age of 18 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under age 18, without parental consent. Children under the age of 18 should not provide their personal information to us.
* **International Data Transfers.** As a multi-national company, we transmit information between and among our affiliates. As a result, your information may be processed in a foreign country where privacy laws may be less stringent than the laws in your country. Nonetheless, where possible we take steps to treat personal information using the same privacy principles that apply pursuant to the law of the country in which we first received your information. For example, when we transmit information from Europe to the United States, we rely upon Standard Contractual Clauses approved by the European commission for the transfer of data. By submitting your personal information to us you agree to the transfer, storage and processing of your information in a country other than your country of residence including, but not necessarily limited to, the United States. If you would like more information concerning our foreign processing policies and arrangements, including attempts to apply the privacy principles applicable in one jurisdiction to data when it goes to another jurisdiction you can contact us using the contact information below.
* **Third-Party Applications/Websites.** We have no control over the privacy practices of websites or applications that we do not own. Any personal information that you provide through third party websites, applications or other means will be governed by the privacy policies applicable to those third parties and mediums.
* **Changes to This Privacy Policy.** We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes to our practices, technology, legal requirements and other factors. When changes are made to this Privacy Policy, they will become immediately effective when published. You can check the “Last Updated” legend at the bottom of this page to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised.

### Additional Information for California Residents

If you are a California resident, you can read more on the [**Additional California Disclosures page**](https://www.thecloroxcompany.com/privacy/california-residents/).

### Additional Jurisdiction-Specific Information

Some jurisdictions may have additional information available. You can read more on the [**Additional Jurisdiction-Specific Terms page**](https://www.thecloroxcompany.com/privacy/jurisdiction-specific-terms/).

### Additional Information for Job Applicants

If you apply for a Job with us, you can read more on the [**Job Applicant page**](https://www.thecloroxcompany.com/privacy/disclosures-for-job-applicants/).

* * *

Contact Information
-------------------

If you would like to exercise applicable privacy rights or understand if those rights apply to you, please follow the instructions below to make your request:

| **You are a…** | **Website (example)** | **Contact Instructions** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| U.S. resident | All U.S. consumer websites | [Visit our Data Subject Request Form](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/65ca6b46-70b1-4ee1-9074-7a63e800ea4c/7baf0e2e-4724-44fe-af48-4138faca9d23) to complete and submit a request. Alternatively, you may call us at [855-545-2325](tel:855-545-2325). |
| U.S. resident | All U.S. B2B websites (e.g., [www.cloroxpro.com](https://www.cloroxpro.com/), [www.hiddenvalleykitchens.com](https://www.hiddenvalleykitchens.com/), etc.) | [Visit our Data Subject Request Form](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/65ca6b46-70b1-4ee1-9074-7a63e800ea4c/7baf0e2e-4724-44fe-af48-4138faca9d23) to complete and submit a request. Alternatively, you may call us at [855-545-2325](tel:855-545-2325). |
| Residents outside of the U.S. | All consumer websites outside of the U.S. | Visit our [International Data Subject Request Form](https://www.thecloroxcompany.com/privacy/dsar/?lang=en) to complete and submit a request. Alternatively, you may email us at [privacyinfo@clorox.com](mailto:privacyinfo@clorox.com). |
| Job Applicant | All job applicants | If you are a job applicant and would like to make a request concerning your Privacy Rights, please email [people@clorox.com](mailto:people@clorox.com) or call [1-800-256-7693](tel:800-256-7693). |

_If you have a question about your privacy rights or otherwise would like to submit a request to exercise such rights, but the options above do not apply to you, please send an email to [privacyinfo@clorox.com](mailto:privacyinfo@clorox.com)._

If you have any questions, comments, or complaints concerning our privacy practices, or if you need to access this Privacy Policy in an alternative format due to having a disability, please contact us at the appropriate address below. We will attempt to respond to your requests and to provide you with additional privacy-related information.

Privacy Team  
Clorox Consumer Services  
PO Box 24305,  
Oakland, California, 94623-1305  

If you are not satisfied with our response, you may have a right to lodge a complaint with your government privacy regulator.

Last Updated and Effective Date: December 8, 2023
